hey guys let's subtract two numbers that
are in binary notation so we do one
minus one which gives us zero zero minus
zero which gives us zero one minus zero
which gives us one and then zero minus
one we can't do so we're gonna have to
borrow so we're gonna scratch out this
one and make it a zero and we're going
to be basically borrowing two for this
column for binary a one in this column
is equal to two in this column and then
two minus one gives us one and then we
have another zero minus one which we
can't do so we're going to borrow again
and making this a two two minus one
gives us one and then once again we
can't do zero minus one so we have to
borrow but we can't borrow from here we
have to borrow all the way from over
here so that gives us a two here so
we're going to make this two a one so we
can move one over here but a one in this
column is equal to a two in this column
and two minus one is equal to one and
then one minus one is zero and then zero
minus zero is zero so we don't need
these last two zeros so one zero one one
zero one zero one minus one one one one
zero zero one is equal to one one one
one zero zero and here's the same
problem in decimal notation 181 minus
one twenty one equals sixty how exciting